premam.in 2018-05-20

# facebook fun Apps | Regional facebook celebrity apps

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at witalks2014@gmail.com.

Witalks is concerned to protect the users privacy. The privacy policy is available to public at all times. We will notify you the changes made in the privacy policy in this page.   
Information we receive   
We collect information from third party sources predominantly Facebook.   
If you log in to witalks using Facebook we receive the following information.   
1\. Facebook username   
2\. Gender   
3\. Email Address   
4\. Facebook profile picture   
5\. Age range   
6\. If a user willing to share the generated results behalf of him we need public_actions.   
We receive the information through Facebook consent box.   
Some apps requires the special permissions from the users.   
The information like user photos, friends list, public posts can also be received by seeking the permission of users through Facebook consent box.   
Your information you provide to us is used only to generate the results for the games you play or the quizzes you take. We do not store your information on our server, nor we provide it to 3rd parties. 

**Privacy on user data.**   
1.User data will only be provided when using automated tests, in which a minimum of basic information is required to perform it;   
2.The information provided by the users in our application will only be used to generate statistics and other basic information necessary for the creation of the tests;   
3.We also reserve the right to disclose information collected about users whose disclosure is required by law, judicial process, rules imposed by any governmental body or when such disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or another user   

**Application removal.**   
1.An application removal should be done by the Facebook application panel itself;;   
2.Any guidelines, if necessary, on unlinking the application with your account, must be made by Facebook itself;   
3.By disassociating you will not be able to connect to the application using Facebook;.   
4.The publications made by the application will be removed from your Timeline if you unlink it with your account. 

**Log Files**   
Like many other Web sites, www.witalks.in makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.witalks.in does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.witalks.in.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.witalks.in and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.witalks.in send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.witalks.in has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.witalks.in's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

Contact person Protection and handling complaints is a concerned issue at witalks. Please contact Hari for any complaints regarding privacy issues. sriharigolla.2785@gmail.com
